elecrow.com 2019-08-13

# Privacy Policy

Elecrow respects all users' privacy, and make it strict policy to protect the information generated by users on our official site https://www.elecrow.com/. Please note this privacy policy only applies to all information collected or submitted on this site. It does not necessarily apply to any offline collection of your personal information.

#### **Collection of User's Information**

When you register an account, place an order, get in touch with elecrow.com, we will have access to your email-address and any other information you need to or choose to provide us for the purpose of making the deal. We collect information to provide specific benefits to our website visitors and allow us to fulfill your order or requests.

#### **Protection of User's Information**

Elecrow ensures that user's information collected on this website is only used for providing service and fulfilling order for user such as products manufacturing and order shipment. We will not sell, transfer, make other use of users' information for financial gain or competitive advantage.

#### **Shipping Providers**

Elecrow offers shipping service for each order through third parties such as DHL, EMS, FedEx, UPS, HongKong Post and the United States Postal Service. We pass delivery addresses, phone numbers, and invoices to these companies to the extent required for quoting shipping prices and successful delivery of orders.

#### **Payment Providers**

When using PayPal to checkout on elecrow.com, a user should provide their PayPal email address. The user will then be directed to paypal.com to complete their payment, after which they will be redirected to elecrow.com to complete the order. In case you do not have a Paypal account, credit card data including the cardholder name, credit card number, expiration date, CVV, and full billing address are sent to Paypal via an API for processing. Details regarding orders are not sent to Paypal. Each transaction is logged by retaining the transaction amount, the customer’s name, addresses and phone numbers. No any credit card data is stored at any point on Elecrow’s servers.

#### **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We may disclose aggregated, anonymous data to investors and potential partners.

#### **Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

Users represent that you have been fully aware of this Privacy Policy and agree with it when using our official site. Users signify acceptance of any modifications by using our official site.

#### **Revision for Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We advise users to check this Privacy Policy frequently to get the current update. The updated Privacy Policy shall bind users as well as the activities made by users on the site when such update is made.

#### **Contact us**

For any question or comments about this Privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at:

West of F-building 8th floor,

Fusen industry park ,

Gushu Hangcheng road ,Bao'an Ave,

Shenzhen city,

China

+86 0755-23204330
